Banu Tryon Fullstack Engineer

Banutryon@gmail.com

Seattle, WA

(425)903-2506

<u>LinkedIn</u> Portfolio

SUMMARY

As a software engineer, I will take my previous experiences and apply them to the projects at hand and provide a solution to your users that will make your company proud. My passion to improve people's lives through technology will allow me to put in the work to make sure we understand the customer at a high level and create world-class products.

SKILLS

Frontend // React, React Native, Redux, HTML, CSS Backend // JavaScript, MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Postgres, Other tools // Github, Figma, Slack

PROJECTS

Marvel info Deck: pulling from an API

• Built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery and AJAX

<u>Tryon-experiences</u>: Tour guide app

• Created a full CRUD app using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Mongoose, Express and EJS

Magic 8 Ball: 8 Ball app that uses Gif's as answers to your questions

• Built using MERN Stack (Mongoose, Express, React, Node.js)-Styled with CSS.

<u>Tesla App:</u> Tesla model S range calculator

• Built using MERRN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Redux, Node.js.)-Styled with CSS.

EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNT MANAGER // GARTEN // SEATTLE

2019-2020

- Lead team to become the top-performing city in my company after two months on the job.
- Built strong client relationships that produced additional 1.5 million dollars above budget...

TERRITORY RESELLER MANAGER // Bose Corp. // Seattle 2016-2019

- Demonstrated the complete ownership of revenue sales resulting in an average yearly quota of 35 million (covering 5 states and 350+ storefronts)
- Experience in making big decisions and creating innovations that impacted hundreds of thousands of customers.
- Built a culture of accountability, became one of the top-ranked territories in the nation for 5 years straight.

REGIONAL ADVOCACY REP // BOSE CORP. // SEATTLE 2012-2016

- Led territory and store-level training utilizing strategic business planning and goal setting to ensure joint execution focused on brand building and targeted sales growth.
- Through team collaboration, delivered national sales training for major retailers. (this includes trade shows, district/ regional trainings)

EDUCATION